instantfundas.com 2012-10-14

# Instant Fundas - All Things Technology and More

by 

Instant Fundas respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding it while you are online at our site. The following privacy policy is to help you understand what information we collect, how it is used and who will have access to that information.

### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet Service Provider (ISP), browser type, operating system you use, referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, number of clicks to different pages, time spent on the site etc. These data are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use this information purely for internal review to enhance the content and/or layout of our website, analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information about the nature of our visitors.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of file stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. This site use cookies to track returning visitors. These cookies does not collect any information about the user. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site too (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (powered by FeedBlitz), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. These information are safeguarded and we do not release our email lists to any third party. Neither do we use it for promotions or any purposes other than delivering content from this site.

### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We do not have access to this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Changes to Privacy Policy

While we do not intend to make changes to this policy very often, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time. If our information practices changes in future we will change or supplement this Privacy Policy accordingly. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Email: admin@instantfundas.com

* * *
